# Alexandru Jina

QA Automation Tester - Manual Tester - QA freelancer

Aleea Garbau nr.6 Cluj Napoca, (0770) 376 762 alexandru.jina@gmail.com

#### **TESTING EXPERIENCE**

# Linnify- QA Engineer

I learned more about web testing, and worked on different projects. My technical skills improved and I became better at identifying and documenting bugs. My responsibilities included: Manual testing strategy, Functionality testing, Regression testing, Bug validation, Exploratory and Test automation. I also learned to use Jira and testrail for test and project management.

# **Azimut Vision - Automation Testing Course**

I learned the basics of setting up automation testing with tools like Selenium and Junit. Since getting my state approved certification, I have been growing my skills and learned more about selenium and how you can use it in different contexts.

I also have basic knowledge of html, css and SQL. Persistence is the road to success and I am practicing and improving my skills everyday.

### Manual testing experience

Self though manual tester. I learned different techniques for manual testing such as: Equivalence partitioning, Boundary Value Analysis, State Transition Testing and so on. I also learned about different types of testing such as: Smoke Testing, Security Testing, Stress Testing, Acceptance Testing, Api testing and so on.

#### Occasional Test Conferences and Events

I participate in occasional test related events in the community.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Linnify, Cluj Napoca - Quality Assurance Engineer

August2022 - Present

Responsible for the QA process for entire projects. Discovered and documented bugs. Performed bug validation and regression testing. Presented Regression reports and kept Qa data up to date. Automated tests using cypress and javascript in order to ease the manual efforts.

# QuanticLab, Cluj Napoca - Quality Assurance Analyst

April 2022 - August 2022

Responsible for performing testing tasks with limited supervision. Report existing bugs or problems. Evaluate functionality on different platforms. Make a daily report on a project.

#### **SKILLS**

Cypress, Javascript, Selenium WebDriver, Java, JUnit, Git, ExtentReport.
Ability to use Jira, Testrail, Confluence.
Good communication skills.
Client oriented attitude.
Good command of the office suite.

#### **OTHER**

Certificate of participation at TestFlix 2021,2023

#### **LANGUAGES**

Romanian

English

# Emerson, Cluj Napoca — Customer Service Administrator

AUG 2021 - MARCH 2022

Responsible for managing and conducting due diligence on orders sent by customers in the Middle East. This position made me more detail oriented and accustomed to high workloads. I became more capable of managing my time and efforts into booking the orders as well as following up with clients and business partners.

# **Yardi Romania,** Cluj Napoca — Customer Service Representative

JULY 2018 - JUNE 2021

Responsible for answering all inbound calls and emails from clients, website users, prospective residents and residents living in apartment communities across the United States;

## Fan Courier, Cluj Napoca — Courier Driver

JUNE 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2017

At this job, I was responsible for delivering packages and handling returns

#### **EDUCATION**

# Azimut Vision - Automation Testing Course, Cluj Napoca

JUNE 2021 - NOVEMBER 2021

Learned how to set up automation testing frameworks.

Learned the basics of Software Quality assurance and the fundamentals of testing.

# Faculty of Letters - UBB, Cluj Napoca

Completed two years of study.

Developed good online research capabilities and excellent written English skills through the various theoretical papers that had to be written; advanced my public speaking abilities as well as my presentation skills by participating in multiple conferences and formal discussions;

#### **PROJECTS**

https://github.com/AJinaEugen/ExempluProiectAJina.git